《法外情真》前情提要
Previously the The Guardian.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
这是你想要的吗
This is what you want?
不  我不想
No, I don't wanna be.
你想作爸爸吗
Do you wanna be a father?
我不想结婚只是因为我怀孕了
I don't wanna get married just because I'm pregnant.
呃  我不在乎你嫁不嫁给我
uh I don't care if you don't want to marry me.
没关系的  我只是
It's alright, I just...
我知道我做好了作父亲的准备
I know that I'm ready to be a father.
你的伴儿呢
Where's your date?
她走了
She left.
早上好  法林先生
Morning, Mr. Fallin.
明天见  法林先生
See you tomorrow, Mr. Fallin.
- 尼古拉斯  - 跟医生谈得怎么样
- Nicholas. - How did it go with the doctor?
查出来我的动脉里有堵塞
Evidently I've got a little blockage.
有多少
Yeah? How much?
五条动脉有四条有堵塞  百分之八十五
Four out of five arteries, 85 percent.
- 需要做手术吗  - 是的
- So you need surgery? - Yeah.
- 那什么时候做手术  - 我不知道
- Well, when you gonna go in? - I don't know.
我想  几个月后吧
A few months, I guess.
- 几个月  - 是的
- A few months? - Yeah.
为什么现在不做
Why not right now?
因为  第一  我们现在正在忙奥尼克斯・弗莱特公司合并的事
Well, in the first place, we're right in the middle of that Onyx Freight merger.
爸  那是我的事情  我一个人可以搞定
Oh, Dad, that's my deal. I can take care of that alone.
尼古拉斯  我们已经和詹姆斯・富勒合作很久了了
Nicholas, we've been working with James Fuller for a long time now.
这事儿比较棘手
That's a little tricky.
你不能因为富勒就先不做手术了啊
You shouldn't let Fuller stop you from having the surgery.
问题是  我想让胡特医生给我做手术
Well, the real problem is that surgeon I want, Dr. Hutter?
- 哦  - 但是在接下来的八周  他都在曼谷
- Right. - Bangkok for the next eight weeks.
你要等他回来吗
Are you're going to wait for him to get back?
是的
Yeah.
第三季  第十集
法外真情
翻译   假   惺惺
校对  油 球
特效  转轮 枪
尼克
Nick.
那是什么
What's that?
这是客户送的一幅画
Oh, it's just a picture from a client.
好有爱
Oh, that's sweet.
是啊
Yeah.
我找到了一个房地产经纪人
So, I think I found a realtor.
我很喜欢她  她叫潘妮
A realtor that I like. Her name's Penny.
她主要在莎迪赛德和东方自由工作
She works primarily in Shadyside and East Liberty.
她就是我们要找的人
She knows exactly what we're looking for.
好的
Okay.
而且她已经找到了几个很棒的地方  所以
And she's already found some great places, so...
我来看看你什么时候有空
I just wanted to check your schedule.
我随时都行
Well...whenever you want.
- 随时吗  - 随时
- Whenever? - Whenever.
那好
Okay.
你好  我是尼克・法林
Hi, this is Nick Fallin.
你是贝蒂吗  你好
ls this Betty? Yeah, hi.
加里森医生说你手里有份
Dr. Garrison said that you would have a list
可以给我父亲做手术的心脏外科医生名单
of available heart surgeons for my father.
好的  好的  谢谢你  贝蒂  谢谢
Okay. Okay. Well, thank you, Betty. I appreciate it.
有人生病了吗
ls someone sick?
一个朋友  心脏有点问题
Just a friend. He has a heart problem.
我15岁的时候我爸因为心脏病发作去世了
Oh. My dad died of a heart attack when I was 15.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我想说的是  我被分到了一个叫克里斯托弗・拉普的孩子的案子
Anyway, I was just assigned to this kid, Christopher Rapp.
露露说  去年他是你的客户
Lulu said that he was your client Iast year.
不记得了
Don't remember him.
他在训练营遇到了麻烦
Well, he's in some trouble over at Summit Boot Camp.
克里斯在两个月前被安置到了训练营
Chris was placed at Summit two months ago.
为什么
Why?
跟一个八岁的女生发生了一些过节
Had a problem with an eight-year-old girl.
- 什么过节？  - 很显然  他摸了那个女孩
- Problem? - Apparently he touched her.
- 好吧  - 所以他不是被抓到训练营就是在教管所
- Okay. - So it was either Summit or Juvie.
- 他几岁了  - 十五岁
- How old is he? - 15.
上周他惹了麻烦  在食堂打架斗殴
Last week he got into some trouble, started a fire in the mess hall.
训练营的头就把他锁在柜子里关了两天
Head of the camp locked him in a closet for two days.
这就是我们这次过来的原因
That's why we're here.
走  集合
Let's go! Fall in!
我们可没那么多时间  各位先生  集合  排好队
We don't have all day, gentlemen! Let's go! Line up!
快走  快走
Move it! Come on, gentlemen!
- 你好  法林先生  - 你好  克里斯
- Hey, Mr. Fallin. - Hey, Chris.
你是谁
Who are you?
我叫苏珊娜・佩尔  我被分配和法林先生一起参与你的案子
I am Suzanne Pell. I'm assigned to your case with Mr. Fallin.
- 你很漂亮  - 谢谢
- You're really pretty. - Thanks.
不用谢
That's okay.
坐吧
Have a seat.
额  苏珊娜  我和他单独聊一会儿吧
Uh, Suzanne, can you give us a minute?
谢谢
Thank you.
我听说你在食堂打架了
So I heard you started a fire.
额
Uh...
我妈过生日  他们都不让我见见我妈
Well, they wouldn't let me see my mom for her birthday.
我妈过生日  我一定要陪她的
I always see my mom for her birthday.
一定
Always.
在这里苦不苦啊
You having a hard time here?
苦
Yeah.
虽然这里有很酷的人
I mean, there are some cool people here.
但是这里大部分的人都不好
Mostly not.
我也挺喜欢这里的这位辅导员的
And the counselors, I like a few of them,
但是有几个辅导员让我们打架  然后他们赌我们谁赢谁输
but a couple a guys make us fight, and they bet on us.
- 你举报了吗  - 只跟你们说了
- Did you report this? - Just to you guys.
大部分孩子都讨厌我
I mean, most of the kids hate me.
有一次他们还让我吃泥巴
They made me eat mud once.
他们偷我的鞋
They stole my shoes.
我都能接受  但是
And I can take that, but...
但是  那次辅导员把我锁在柜子里
But when that counselor did that thing, locked me in the closet,
我好想见我妈
I just wanted to see my mom.
好吧  克里斯  我看看我能做点儿什么
All right, Chris. Well, I'll see what I can do.
- 你能帮我离开这里吗  - 我会尽力
- You'll get me out of here? - I'll see what I can do.
谢谢你
Thank you.
像我之前说的那样
Like I said before.
鉴于当时的情况  那样处罚他是合理的
He was punished appropriately, given the circumstances.
你有没有把他锁在柜子里
Did you lock him in a closet?
他只是被合理地惩罚了
He was punished appropriately.
- 真是讲不通  - 是啊
- What a tool. - Yeah.
我们把孩子救出来吧
Well, you know, let's try and get this kid out of here.
他们会把他送到教管所的
They'll just send him to Juvie.
也许我们可以好好跟法官谈一谈
Well, maybe we can work something out with the judge.
好的
Okay.
- 尼克  - 什么事
- Nick? - Yeah?
那天聚餐的晚上
About the other night at the party.
就那样发生了  我不是有意让你不舒服的
It just happened, and I didn't mean to make you feel uncomfortable.
我不是那种随随便便  在衣帽间亲男人的女人
I don't exactly go around kissing men in coat rooms.
爸
Dad?
嗨  尼克
Hey, Nick.
嗨
Hey.
- 有事吗  - 没事
- What's up? - Nothing.
- 你在这边吃吗  - 还没
- You eating over? - No.
我爸在家吗
ls my dad here?
在的
Yeah.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
- 我就说  好像听到你的声音了  - 是啊
- Thought I heard you. - Yeah.
香农  我想跟我爸单独说两句
Uh, Shannon, I have to speak with my dad.
工作的事情吗
Work stuff?
是的
Yeah.
亲爱的  好不好
Okay, honey?
好的
Okay.
你要不要坐下来说
Hey, uh, do you want to sit down?
好的
Okay.
怎么了
What's going on?
我跟  你在喝什么
I spoke to-- What are you drinking?
苏格兰威士忌
Scotch.
是啊
Yeah.
我今天去找过加里森医生了
I went to see Dr. Garrison today.
是吗
Did you.
他认为你应该现在就做手术
He thinks you should have the surgery now.
他还说胡特医生是东海岸最好都的心脏外科医生呢
He also thinks Dr. Hutter is the best heart surgeon on the East Coast.
你可能撑不到胡特医生回来
Well, you may not live to have Dr. Hutter do your procedure.
他之前给罗恩・哈西  摩西・保罗和杰里・斯蒂芬斯都做过手术
Well, he did Ron Hassey, Moses Paul, and Jerry Stephens.
他们对他的评价非常高  但是我确定他们
And they think very highly of him, but I'm sure Dr. Hutter
被确诊的时候胡特医生没有去泰国度假
wasn't on a vacation in Thailand when they were diagnosed.
我这里有份名单  上面有三个医生 他们都有时间做手术并且口碑都不错
I have a list here of three surgeons, all available and all highly recommended.
马基塔医生
Dr. Makita.
我们之前告过他
We sued him.
约翰・西格尔  我之前有跟他一起打过网球
John Siegel. I used to play tennis with him.
我一直不喜欢他
I never liked the guy.
那么  就剩下帕特里夏・德里斯科尔了
Well, then it's Patricia Driscoll.
上面写着她是从医科大学毕业九年了
It says she graduated med school nine years ago?
是啊
Right.
那她现在多大
How old is she?
我不知道  也许38吧
I don't know. Maybe 38?
不可能
No way.
爸  如果你不做手术 结果心脏病发作了
Dad, if you don't do this and you have a heart attack,
那么情况就不一样了
then it's a whole new ballgame.
尼古拉斯  有点经验不是什么坏事
Nicholas, you know, a little experience wouldn't hurt.
希望你可以考虑考虑名单上的医生
Well, I'd really appreciate if you'd consider someone on that list.
我要当爸爸了
I'm gonna have a baby.
露露怀孕了  而且
Lulu's pregnant and...
我希望孩子出生的时候  你还在  还能看到他们
You know, I just hope that you're gonna be around to meet your grandkids.
有三个车库
There's a three-car garage
而且主卧太棒了  你不觉得吗
and the master bedroom is spectacular, don't you think?
所以  你喜欢吗
So, how do you like it?
你有没有四处转转
Well, have you looked around?
有啊
Yeah.
你知道吗  他们这套房子唯一不足的地方就是
You know, the only mistake that they made with this house
他们没有在正门进来的地方建一间化妆室
is not having a powder room at the front entrance.
但是我在想  你可以把那个柜子敲掉  然后放一个淋浴室
But I was thinking, you could knock that closet out and put a half-bath in.
好  我能跟你说说我是怎么想的吗
Yeah, can I tell you what I'm thinking about,
或者你能不能说说你的想法
or would you like to form your own opinion?
我再看看
I'm trying very hard to form my own opinion.
好吧
Right.
我带你去看看后院
Um, let me show you the backyard.
好的  你要一起来吗
Oh, okay. You want to come?
我随后就来
I'll catch up.
好的
Okay.
- 嗨  - 你是尼克吗
- Hi. - You're Nick?
你是斯科尔医生吗  谢谢你能见我
Dr. Driscoll? Thanks for your time.
我可以为你做什么
What can I do for you?
关于我父亲伯顿・法林  我有几个问题想要请教你
I just wanted to ask you some questions about my father, Burton Fallin.
我看过他的病历了  他需要手术
I've seen his chart. He needs surgery.
这样的手术你做过几次
How many of these procedures have you performed?
150次
150.
希望你不要介意  我能问下你做这种手术的成功率是多少吗
lf you don't mind my asking, what is your success rate?
这是心脏手术  但是我的死亡率
lt's heart surgery, but my fatality rate
与其他顶级胸外科医生的死亡率一样
is consistent with every other top thoracic surgeon.
你觉得胡特医生怎么样
What do you think of Dr. Hutter?
我觉得他很厉害  我就是他教的
I think he's good. He trained me.
如果你是想问我有没有把握做这个手术  我的答案是非常有把握
lf you're asking if I can handle it, my answer is absolutely.
太棒了  谢谢
Great. Thank you.
爸
Dad.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
我刚才去见了斯科尔医生  她很厉害
I just met with Dr. Driscoll. She's very impressive.
我在想你能不能见见她
You know, I thought maybe if you just met with her--
哦  不  谢谢你  但是我还是想继续等
Oh, no. I appreciate that, but I think I'm gonna just wait.
胡特才是我要的医生  至少我是这么想的
Hutter's my guy. At least that's the way I see it.
另外  合并的事情马上就要开始了
And besides that, the Onyx deal is really heating up now, so...
你说的这些有证据吗
Do you have any proof of these claims?
他是这么跟我说的
Just his word.
训练营的头  威尔金森先生
And the head of the camp, Mr. Wilkinson--
威尔金森长官肯定会捍卫他在训练营的地位
Sergeant Wilkinson is clearly going to protect his position at the camp.
他说什么都没发生
He says that nothing happened.
佩尔小姐  你有没有提交事故报告
Ms. Pell, have you filed an incident report?
提交了
I have.
那就让警察去调查吧
Then let the state look into it.
但是这样对我的当事人没有任何帮助
But that doesn't help my client, Your Honor.
你是在说让我把他送到教改所吗
You're asking me to send your client to Juvenile Detention?
不是  我是在请求您帮他找到一个适合他的地方
No, I'm asking you to let me find him an appropriate placement.
这已经是我第二次看到你当事人的案子了
Your client has been in front of me twice.
上次他猥亵了一个8岁的小女孩
The last time for molesting an eight-year-old girl.
是的
That's correct.
在警方的调查结果出来之前
I'll wait for the state's report on the camp.
克里斯还是待在他现在的地方
But for now, Chris stays where he is.
总之  那次是我第一次也是最后一次网恋
Anyway, that was the first and the last time that I ever dated on the Internet.
- 他当时多大  - 我不知道  18岁吧
- How old was he? - I don't know. 18?
但是  我还是很怀念高中生活的
But I'm thinking high school.
嗨  尼克
Hey, Nick.
- 嗨  苏珊娜  - 嗨  露露
- Hi, Suzanne. - Hi, Lulu.
- 你现在有空吗  - 当然
- Do you have a second? - Sure.
- 你需不需要我打给克里斯  - 不用  我来吧
- Do you want me to call Chris? - No, I got it.
你考虑那个房子了吗
So, have you thought about that house?
潘妮给我打电话了  她说房主
Because Penny called, and she thinks the owners
就要降价了
are gonna come down on the price.
那是因为他们之前的价格要得太高了
Well, that's because they're asking too much.
是的  但是如果他们降价
Yeah, but then, you know, if they do that,
就会有很多人会去看房子的
a whole new group of buyers will go and look at it.
你想要吗
Do you want it?
不是  我只是觉得那套房子很适合我们俩  还有我们的宝宝
No, I just think it really works for us... with the baby.
有升值的空间
There's room to grow.
你确定吗
You're not sure?
不  我挺喜欢的  我只是
No, I like it. I just, uh...
上次参观的时候  我有点分心
Uh, I was a little distracted Iast time I was there.
那我们再去看一次好了
Well, let's go look at it again.
你知道的  如果我们想要  不是现在  我是说几年后
And, you know, if we want to-- Not now but in a few years,
我们可以把那堵墙敲掉  然后造一个厨房
we could knock down that wall and open up the kitchen
那样的话就会很显得大了
and then it would be a really open plan.
是啊  这套房子的结构很不错
Oh, yeah. It has great bones.
你想怎么弄就怎么弄
So, any way you want to go.
这里的分区很自由的
Oh, and the zoning around here, very liberal.
新建还是拆除  或者保持原样
So, build up, build out, orjust leave it as is.
由你们决定
lt's turnkey.
潘妮  这房子多少钱
What's it gonna cost, Penny?
我觉得我们可以在要价的基础上优惠五万吧
I think we can get it for 50 under the asking price.
能不能让我们商量下
Can you give us a second, please?
- 当然  - 谢谢
- Oh, sure. - Thanks.
那  你想不想要
Well, uh, do you want it?
这是我见过的里面最好的了
Well, it's the best I've seen.
是啊  但是你想不想要
Right. But do you want it?
我想要  你呢
Yeah, I do. Do you?
如果你能付得起的话  当然可以
Well, if you can figure out how to pay for it.
什么意思  你把你的房子卖了  我把我的房子卖了
What do you mean? You sell your house. I sell my house.
就可以申请大额抵押贷款
Get a big mortgage.
但是我们有工作
Yeah, but we're both working.
嗯  你知道  你的工资
Well, you know, you're income's, uh...
我们都想要这太房子  所以为什么不我把房子买下  然后你跟我住呢
We both want it. So why don't I just buy it, and we can live here together?
不  我想和你一起买
No, I want to buy it with you.
你不想结婚
You don't want to get married,
但是你想跟我一起还贷款
but you want to get into a 30-year mortgage with me.
谁啊
Yeah?
他伤得很严重吗
How badly hurt is he?
好的  你现在在训练营吗
Right. Are you there at Summit now?
好的  你需要我去吗
Okay. Do you need me?
好的
Good.
好的  明天卢茨法官那边见面
All right, tomorrow at Judge Lutz's.
好的  再见
Yeah. Bye.
是谁啊
Who was that?
苏珊娜・佩尔
Suzanne Pell.
怎么了
What's going on?
一个客户  克里斯・拉普  想要逃出训练营
A client, Chris Rapp, he tried to escape from Summit.
被辅导员抓到了  揍了一顿
Counselor that caught him beat him up.
可怜的孩子
Poor kid.
是啊
Yeah.
尼克  关于房子
You know, Nick, about the house...
都是为了孩子  对吗  为了我们的孩子
lt's for the baby, right? Our baby.
所以我想我们应该
So that's why I think that we really should just-
什么事
Yeah?
苏珊娜・佩尔真的有必要在半夜三点给你打电话吗
Does Suzanne Pell really need you at 3:OO in the morning?
好吧
All right.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
我跟加里森医生谈过了
I spoke to Dr. Garrison.
好消息事这不是心脏病发作
Good news is it wasn't a heart attack.
是啊  我也觉得不是
Yeah, I didn't think so.
我这是上楼去拿香烟
Just walking up the stairs to get some cigarettes and...
突然就呼吸不过来了
I couldn't get my breath.
胸口紧绷
Tightness in the chest.
你知道吗  德里斯科尔医生  呃
You know, this Dr. Driscoll, um...
她就是胡特医生教出来的  而且她有空
She was trained by Dr. Hutter, and she's available.
是
Right.
你要不要做手术
You want to do it?
好吧  我觉得可以做了
Well, I guess it makes sense.
好的  那我去安排下
Okay, I'll schedule it.
明天早上9点  奥尼克斯的人会
Tomorrow morning at 9, the guys from Onyx
去办公室谈合并的事情
are coming over to the office to talk over the merger.
我知道  我来安排会议
I know. I set the meeting.
好
Hmm.
我觉得这次会议的关键是保留条款
I think the key is that hold-back provision.
富勒会尽可能把钱托管
Fuller's gonna want to keep as much money in escrow as--
爸
Dad.
我会处理的
Just let me deal with it.
好的  好吧
Yeah, right.
你跟他们说我有些私事要处理
Maybe let's just tell them I got some personal situation to take care of.
- 私事  - 是啊
- Personal situation? - Yeah.
不要什么都告诉他们
Just... be vague.
为什么
Why not just tell the truth?
他们有可能会解雇我们
They might fire us.
尼古拉斯  我不是想侮辱你
Nicholas, I'm not trying to insult you.
我已经给富勒打过三场案子了
I've closed three deals for Fuller.
我也为他工作了5年了  他知道我是什么样的律师
I've worked for him for five years. He knows what kind of lawyer I am.
- 好  - 好吧
- Right. - Right, well...
不要把话说死
Be vague.
他怎么样了
How is he?
他们给他安排了明天的手术
They scheduled his surgery for tomorrow.
不妨就把病都治好
Might as well get it over with.
对啊
Exactly.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hi. - Hey.
饿了吗
You hungry?
不饿
No.
好吧  我给你准备了一把新的牙刷
All right. Well, I put a new toothbrush for you.
就在大厅那边的洗手间里
lt's in the bathroom down the hall over there.
那里还有毛巾  肥皂  沐浴露
And there's towels and soap and shampoo and all that.
我在书房的沙发上给你铺了床
I pulled out the sofa bed for you, too, in the den.
铺得不好  不好意思
lt's kinda lumpy though. Sorry.
还有什么
What else?
你要不要子在上学前稍微睡一会儿
Do you want to try and get some sleep before school?
我今天能不能待在家
Can't I just stay home today?
不行  我们得工作
No, we have to work.
好吧
Right.
伯顿会不会死啊
ls Burton gonna die?
不会  他
No, he...
如果他死了
lf he dies--
香农  能不能不要说了  他不会死的  好吗
Shannon, could you just stop it? He's not gonna die, okay!
我跟克伦威尔・斯温的马特・邓恩聊过了
I spoke to Matt Dunn at Cromwell-Swain.
你爸不来开会了吗
Your father's not coming to this meeting?
不来了  所以  邓恩说保留条款没有问题
No. So Dunn is okay with the hold-back provision. He says no problem.
他没跟我说他今天不来
He didn't tell me that he wasn't coming to this meeting.
他有私事要处理
He has a personal situation to attend to.
在12页上  我们可以看到
On page 12, you will see that the--
等等  等等
Wait. Wait.
什么意思  什么私事
What do you mean, a personal situation?
私事
A personal situation.
你们能不能出去一下
You guys want to gives us a minute here?
谢谢
Thank you.
这不像伯顿
This doesn't sound like Burton.
伯顿从1978年以来就没有缺席过会议
urton hasn't missed a meeting since 19T8.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
他健康出了点问题
He has a medical issue.
什么问题
What kind of medical issue?
- 心脏  - 心脏
- Heart. - Heart.
好吧  那我们还是等他回到办公室再谈这件事吧
Okay. So listen, why don't we just wait until he gets back to the office
我们再接着说这件事
and then we'll just finish this up then?
- 你确定吗  - 我确定
- You sure? - Yeah.
- 好吗  - 好吧
- Okay? - All right.
- 哪个医院  - 匹兹堡纪念医院
- What hospital? - Pittsburgh Memorial.
对  我明白  胡特医生事世界顶尖的医生
Yeah, I understand Hutter's world-class.
结果  训练营的一个辅导员就一拳打在他脸上了
As a result, a camp counselor punched him in the face
并且用手电筒袭击了他
and hit him with a flashlight.
缝了七针  身上都是伤
Seven stitches and bruised ribs.
法官大人  请看看我的当事人
Now take a look at my client, Your Honor.
很显然  他不适合待在那里
This is clearly not a good fit.
我们会给他转到新的地方
We'll move him.
谢谢
Thank you.
克里斯今天结束再训练营的时间
Chris completed 70 days at Summit.
我推荐给他结业证书
I recommend that he be given his certificate
将他转到紧急收容所
and placed in an emergency shelter.
可以
Fine.
但是  监狱他之前的罪行
But given the seriousness of Chris' previous omenses,
你要安排对他24小时的监督
you'll need to arrange 24-hour supervision.
在我惹事之前  我一直待在一个地方
There's this place I used to live, before I got in trouble.
也许我能去那里
Maybe I could go there.
不行的
That's not gonna work.
但是我很喜欢待在那里  而且那儿的辅导员也喜欢我
But I liked it there a lot, and the head counselor liked me.
- 尼克  行不行  - 没得选
- Nick? - It's not an option.
你们能不能带我去见我妈
Could one of you take me to go see my mom?
你去了收容所肯定会安排的
I'm sure something can be arranged when you get to the shelter.
但是我错过了她的生日  她会生气的
But I missed her birthday, and she'll be upset.
我错过了她的生日  他们也不带我去见她
I missed her birthday, and they won't take me to go see her!
他们会跟训练营一样  答应我带我去  结果没有
And it'll be just like boot camp, and they'll say they will and they won't!
他们会忘记我的话  他们不会带我去
They'll forget, and they won't take me!
嗨  嗨
Hi! Hi!
嗨
Hi!
这是我妈妈
That's my mom.
她在睡觉
She's sleeping.
也许你应该让她好好睡觉
Yeah, maybe you should just let her sleep.
不要  她看到我会很开心的
No. She'll be excited to see me.
嗨  妈妈
Hey, Mom.
怎么了
What?
是我  克里斯
lt's Chris.
妈妈  妈妈  是我啊
Ma. Ma, it's Chris.
我刚在睡觉
I was sleeping.
我给你带来了你的生日礼物
I brought you this card for your birthday.
我只想睡觉
I just want to sleep.
但是我给你带礼物了
But I brought you this.
上面写了什么
What's it say?
是一首诗
Um... there's a poem.
不是我写的
I didn't write it.
是他们做卡片的人编的
Something they made up when they made the cards,
我在诗的下面写了  生日快乐
but down here I wrote ''Happy Birthday''
还有  我爱你  你是我的好妈妈
and that I love you and that you're a good mom.
你要不要弹一下钢琴
Are you gonna play the piano?
不
No.
之前有个小孩  时不时会来这里弹琴
There's a kid... comes here sometimes... plays the piano.
不不  是我  克里斯
No. No, Mom. It's me. Chris.
我来给你庆生的
I'm here to celebrate.
我妈之前在一所学校上学  她跟我外婆住
My mom, she used to go to this school, and she lived with my grandma,
学校旁边有个卖糖果的加油站
and there's this gas station near the school that sold candy,
她放学回家的路上会去那里
so she used to go there on her way home.
加油站有个小伙子
And there was this guy. This, you know, gas station guy.
额  怎么说来着
A, um...
- 服务员  - 对
- Attendant. - Yeah.
是的  然后
Right. And, uh...
我想他喜欢我妈  我妈然后怀孕就生下了我
I guess he liked her because she got pregnant and... that's how I was born.
好吧
Right.
我想  他应该不愿意承认他是她的男朋友
But then I guess he didn't really want to admit that he was her boyfriend,
所以  我最后就
so that's why I ended up...
好吧
Okay.
我知道我妈现在脑子不清楚
I know my mom's retarded.
但是我不是
And I know I'm not.
所以你不需要为我感到难过
So you don't have to feel bad or anything.
露露  我一直在考虑房子的事情
You know, I've been thinking, Lulu, about the house.
我要买下它
I'm gonna buy it.
好啊  我也想尽我的一份力
Well, I want to contribute what I can.
哪怕只有一点点的分担
Any percentage of it that I can own--
嗯  只是情况会变得很复杂
Yeah, it just gets very complicated.
- 我知道  但是我觉得  - 我们想要买下它对不对
- I know, but I feel-- - We want it, right?
所以就让我买吧  然后我们再看
So I'm just going to buy it and then we'll see what happens.
- 再看  - 嗯
- See what happens? - Yeah.
尼克  如果你觉得结婚
Nick, if you think that... getting married--
如果你觉得这会让事情简单点
lf you think that that's going to make things easier...
我不是在说结婚的事  我是在说买房子的事情
No, I'm not talking about marriage. I'm talking about buying a house.
嗨  我醒着呢
Hey. I'm awake.
我就闭眼眯了一会儿
Just closed my eyes for a couple a seconds.
你站在这里多久了
How long you been standing there?
刚到
I just got here.
坐吧
Sit down.
富勒今天早上在办公室给我发了一条短信
I got a message from Fuller this morning at the office.
你是不是告诉他我在医院了
Did you tell him I was in the hospital?
呃
Um...
我必须跟他说实话
I had to tell him the truth.
尼古拉斯  我跟你说了
Nicholas, I told you---
爸  我做过合并的案子  我做过很多
Dad, I've done a merger. I've done dozens of them.
- 这不是重点  - 那么重点是什么
- That's not the point. - Then what's the point then?
他可是富勒啊  他身边需要一个固定可靠的律师
lt's Fuller. He needs a certain kind of attorney at his side.
听着  关于孩子的事情
Listen, about this baby thing.
是不是因为孩子你才想结婚的
ls that why you wanted to get married?
你爱她  我可以看得出来
Well, you love this woman. I can see that.
你会是个好父亲的
You'll be a good dad.
爸  关于奥尼克斯的事我很抱歉
Listen, I'm sorry about the Onyx deal.
你想让我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
不用做什么
Nothing.
我已经给他打过电话了  我看看能不能搞定
I'll just call Fuller and see if I can straighten it out.
嗨  我跟香农说我会去接她的
Hey. I told Shannon I'd pick her up.
我可以去接她
I can do that.
是  但是她想去买化妆品
Yeah, but she wants to buy makeup.
那好吧
Okay.
另外  那套房子我申请了
Oh, I made an offer on the house.
- 是吗  - 嗯  申请价格在报价之下
- You did? - Yeah. TO under the asking.
好的  希望你能买到
Okay. Well, I hope you get it.
嗯
Yeah.
待会见
See ya.
这里好像不允许抽烟
I know they don't appreciate smoking up here.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我去收容所看望克里斯  他好像在生什么事的气
I went to see Chris at the shelter. He was upset about something.
生他妈妈的气吗
His mother?
他一直哭  说了一些关于他妈妈的事
He was crying. Said something about her.
我把他带到会议室  想要让他冷静下来
Took him into a meeting room, tried to calm him down.
他打你了吗
He did this to you?
他抓住我  打我  骑在我身上
He grabbed me and hit me and...got on top of me.
撕掉了我的衬衫
Ripped my shirt.
幸亏保安来得很快
Guards came in fast.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我想喝一杯
I could use a drink.
我跟他想要搬到一起住
And so we're talking about moving in together,
他跟我将他是一个存在主义者
and he says to me that he's an existentialist,
他想让我明白什么是存在主义
and that he wants me to understand what it means.
一直跟我说  意思就是  意识就是
He keeps saying, ''What it means.''
我就是听不明白
I don't get it.
我想  他的意思是让我不要指望他太多
I think that he meant that he didn't want me to expect too much from him.
这一切都不重要了  那我们为什么还要纠缠下去呢
Because nothing matters anyway, so why even bother to try.
所以你没有搬去跟他住吗
So you didn't move in with him?
搬了  但是搬去住简直是一场灾难
No, I did. It was a disaster.
是不是我拖着你的时间了
Am I keeping you?
不行
No.
我要拖住你
I'm keeping you.
我喜欢你
I like you.
我不需要你对我负责什么的
I don't care about obligations or whatever.
我都试过了
I've tried that.
我甚至结过婚
I even got married for a while.
我只是想
I just like to...
如果我想感受某件事  我就要去感受
When I feel something, I like to feel it.
我去跳舞了  你不用一起来
I'm gonna dance. You don't have to.
能给我一杯龙舌兰吗
Can I have a shot of tequila?
- 嗨  - 早上好
- Hi. - Morning.
我今天可以去医院吗
May I come to the hospital today?
好吧  需要在医院等很久
Well, it's just going to be a lot of waiting around.
我想去
I'd like to come.
那放学之后去吧
Maybe after school.
我想去  万一  你知道的
I just want to be there, in case... you know.
他没事的
He's gonna be fine.
是的  香农  只是一个很常见的手术
Yeah, It's just a routine operation, Shannon.
但是如果有意外呢
But what if something happens?
那我们会解决的
Then we'll deal with it.
好  但是如果有什么坏事发生呢  我怎么办
Right, but if something goes wrong, what's gonna happen to me?
我住哪儿
Where will I live?
我们会找到地方住的
We'll find a place.
但是我不会跟你住是吧
But not with you?
我不知道
I don't know.
我十一点半去接你  好吗
I'll pick you up at 11 :30, okay?
- 拜拜  - 拜拜
- Bye. - Bye.
- 我需要一个请假条  - 什么
- I'll need a note. - What?
离校的话要写请假条
To get out of school. I'll need a note.
好吧
All right.
老师叫玛莎卡
Miss Mashaka.
- 嗨  - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
我昨天跟你父亲在电话里聊过了
I spoke with your dad on the phone yesterday.
听起来他状态不错
Sounds like he's doing pretty good.
是  目前他身体状况还可以
Yeah, he's doing great, given the circumstances.
嗯  我们都知道伯顿是个硬汉
Well, we both know that Burton is tough.
但是这件事是等不到他
But there's no way that he's gonna get back to this office
回来再结解决了
in time to close this up.
是啊  如您所知  富勒先生
Right. Well, as you know, Mr. Fuller,
我很擅长做合并的案子
I'm perfectly capable of doing this kind of work myself.
是
Yes.
我雇了兰达尔・柯克的公司
I hired Randall Kirk's firm.
兰达尔・柯克
Randall Kirk.
他会接受这个案子的
He's gonna be taking over this deal.
好的
Right.
你能不能把资料交给他  跟他把事情的进展交代清楚
So, if you could get him the files and bring him up to speed?
当然
Yeah. Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗨
Hi.
我找尼克・法林
I'm here to see Nick Fallin.
嗨
Hey.
我
l...just...
克里斯昨晚从收容所跑掉了
Chris ran away from the shelter last night.
我要被送到教改所了是吧
I'm going to Juvie, right?
我有种感觉
I have these feelings...
一直以来  关于女生
all the time... about girls.
我一看到她们  我就
And when I see them, I just...
我不知道  我
I don't know, l...
我只是有种感觉  她们让我不舒服
I just have these feelings, and they don't make me feel very good.
我不是故意伤害她或者是吓到她的
I didn't mean to hurt her... or scare her.
我只是
I just...
我只是想碰碰她
I just wanted to touch her.
我们走吧  克里斯
Let's go, Chris.
我们走
Let's go.
嗨  你怎么样了
Hey. How you doing?
我很好  你呢
I'm good. I'm good. And you?
还不知道
We'll see.
爸  一切都会好起来的
Dad, it's all gonna be fine.
是啊
Yeah, well...
对
Yeah.
我  呃
l, uh...
我只是  你知道的
I just... you know...
我高兴你做手术了
I'm glad you're doing this.
嗯
Yeah.
富勒跟兰达尔・柯克签约了
Fuller signed with Randall Kirk.
他告诉我了
He told me.
我试过挽回他  但是
Yeah, I tried to get him back but...
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
尼古拉斯  听着  手术没问题的
Nicholas, look, this is not gonna be a problem, this operation.
我知道  我知道
I know. I know.
你没什么好担心的  没事的
lt's nothing for you to worry about. It's just... nothing.
嗯
Yeah.
嗯  好的  好吧
Yeah, fine. Right. Okay.
刚才是潘妮打过来的
That was Penny.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是  他们拒绝了我的报价
Yeah. They rejected the offer.
你要不要再跟他们谈谈
You gonna counter?
不用了
No.
好吧
Well...
你一定非常累了
You must be exhausted.
不  没有
No, not really.
你出门的时候很晚了
Well, you were out so late.
是啊
Yeah.
发生什么事了
What happened?
我跟你说过  那个小孩  克里斯  他袭击了社会工作员
I told you. That kid, Chris, he attacked the social worker.
- 苏珊娜  - 是的
- Suzanne. - Right.
揍得不轻
Beat her up.
怎么样了
How'd it go?
四条堵塞的动脉都搞定了
Well, we got all four arteries.
所以他没事了是吗
So he's fine.
手术很成功
It went well.
谢谢你  谢谢
Oh, thank you. Thank you.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
对字幕有任何意见和建议的同学请加Q群：544487177